[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "I mean, but is it like all things in comedy, especially those running things, is it the simpler the idea, often, the more effective it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Who are you most likely to write a thank you note to right now as a comedian -- Anthony Weiner or Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Oh, my gosh!", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anthony Weiner", "Arnold Schwarzenegger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Tough, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Both have been great to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "But for you guys, I mean, brilliant, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "ALLON: It's the best for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "I honestly, purposely have not gone to therapy because I know some crazy stuff's going to be dragged up and, you know, I'll be like, wait, what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "But instinctively your protective shield is comedy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "You don't really want to answer that question, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "No, I mean, I guess it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "How can \"The Tonight Show\" start tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "The tomorrow show, yes, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Why weren't you that popular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Were you drawn to the absurd and the potentially comedic always?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "I don't -- wasn't anybody drive in New York anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I mean, yes, you don't have to.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Did you have a happy childhood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "It was so happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "And apart from the hair, which was outrageous -- what do you think when you watch that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "The striped shirt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Did you love that buzz of laughter coming from people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "I think that was the thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "At some stage in my life, I can do that with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "And we asked Brian if he would do it just Brian Williams and he, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian", "Brian Williams"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A.", "L.A."]}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "When you actually discovered you had the possibility of being on it, what was that moment like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "I think it was like -- you know, I actually auditioned for the show -- I dropped out of school -- college and I went to L.A. to join the Gramlings (ph) which is like the second city of L.A. like improv troupe and learned how to act and act with other people, because when you do standup comedy you don't know how to act with other people because you're on stage by yourself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "Why would you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, you know, you start a show -- a publicist, you know, they control the actors, what publicity they do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What really makes you laugh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "I like -- of course, I love comedians, any comedian.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What kind of things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "British humor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "You know those guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "I do, yes, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "And that's your trademark, I think, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "I think that's my thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "I mean, indisputably, he's endlessly entertaining, isn't he, in all guises?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "He's a smart, smart businessman.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "So, when you get a situation that arose in the way that it did and it creates this awful chasm between them, how do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "It's almost like watching like your family fight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Where do you think the real problem lay in all that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "ALLON: I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Was it -- was it as simple as when Jay was number one, NBC saying to him, you've got five more years, then you have to stop, without thinking in five years' time you might still be number one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", ",", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "RBR", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I think that's bizarre in the first place.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"], "PERSON": ["Jay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay"]}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Do you blame Jay for anything that happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, I don't blame Jay.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Are you a frustrated movie star because you've got the kind of looks for it and you've had a standup movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I don't think I have the look for it, to be honest, to be a leading man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "What I find odd about standup comedians or anyone who's done that is how you ever have the patience for movies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I don't like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "What you working on there dude?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "I got this report that I have to do for next Friday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Sheen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "I mean, hard work because these sketches aren't easy to do, are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Is he winning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Adonis DNA.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Is any part of what's happened with Charlie winning, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Have you had a moment in your life -- not Charlie Sheen- esque, but have you ever got into boozing, drugs, any of the kind of pitfalls that follow comedians, entertainers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Drinking I think is probably the closest I've come to doing anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruce Springsteen"]}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "What's been the most excited you've been about a guest that's come on your show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "Bruce Springsteen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Was he great in real life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "I don't believe in that thing you should never meet your heroes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "Your wife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "I'd be nothing without my wife.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Is she a good critic of your -- of your work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Does she live there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "She lives in New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 796, "question": "Do you find it funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 797, "answer": "I called her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 817, "question": "Can we expect any little Fallons on the way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 818, "answer": "I mean, there might be some right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "How would you feel if you had a child with no sense of humor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "It's impossible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 880, "question": "Do you mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 881, "answer": "Well, I feel unnerved by this, but I'll do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "You sure about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110615pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 912, "question": "Can you do what you're good at, please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", ",", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 913, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]